<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Where I Stand</title><link>https://whereistand.xyz/en/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Where I Stand</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>jihui.yang0.0@gmail.com (Joey)</managingEditor><webMaster>jihui.yang0.0@gmail.com (Joey)</webMaster><copyright>© All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whereistand.xyz/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Same: Same</title><link>https://whereistand.xyz/en/posts/1_same-same/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate><author>jihui.yang0.0@gmail.com (Joey)</author><guid>https://whereistand.xyz/en/posts/1_same-same/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My fascination with jazz started with a story about fake books. The first time I heard the phrase “fake book,” the image that popped into my head was a book whose cover says, “Don’t look, it’s fake.” Later I learned it was something completely different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its “fake” does not mean counterfeit. It means pretending. You can think of a fake book as a lifesaving crib sheet. It usually is not a full score, but a single melody line plus chord symbols, sometimes with lyrics. The purpose is almost embarrassingly practical. Tonight you are playing a regular gig in a bar, a dance hall, or a restaurant. The audience requests songs the way they order dishes, and they do it with an impressive level of confidence. You cannot possibly memorize everything, and you cannot haul a cart of sheet music everywhere you go. So what do you do. You bring a fake book. You flip to the tune. The melody and the harmonic skeleton are there. The rest is on you.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hello, world</title><link>https://whereistand.xyz/en/posts/hello/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>jihui.yang0.0@gmail.com (Joey)</author><guid>https://whereistand.xyz/en/posts/hello/</guid><description>The first post of Where I Stand.</description></item></channel></rss>